(Leonard:)Sheldon, your food's getting cold.
(Sheldon:)I'll eat later. Right now I'm suckling at the
informative bosom of mother physics.
(Penny:)It's hot when Sheldon talks dirty.
So I found this website
where you send them pictures...
(Raj:)...they sculpt your head
and make an action figure out of you.
(Raj:)- How awesome is that?
- Let me see.
(Raj:)You can pick your wardrobe,
you can choose your accessories.
Oh, Leonard,
you can get a little asthma inhaler.
(Leonard:)Oh, this is neat.
(Leonard:)Think about all the action figures
we've bought.
(Leonard:)It would be kind of cool
to have one that look like us.
(Penny:)Yeah, if that's your idea of what's cool,
you should get one.
(Leonard:)Yeah, so I'm out.
What do you think?
Want an action figure that looks like you?
- Would it come with kung-fu grip?
- No.
(Sheldon:)Don't waste my time.
(Leonard:)You get that these
are personalized action figures.
(Penny:)Honey, if you want one, just get one.
- You're still out, right?
- Yup.